Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records
1900 -- 2007
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation
UA042
88.8 Linear Feet 74 boxes
140 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized in two series: Survey and reports and Unprocessed accessions.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains subject files, administrative files, data and final reports of surveys, including Senior Surveys, Twelve College Comparisons, and surveys about salary, faculty, programs, and alumni. In general, the collection contains reports of surveys done on a campus-wide basis. Reports and research done for individual departments or programs are held by the program.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Institutional Planning was founded under the direction of John (Jack) A. Dunn Jr. in 1977. Dunn began publishing the University Fact Book in 1973 while he was Special Assistant for Administration in the Office of the President. In 1977, Dunn was named the Associate Vice President of Planning and the Office of Institutional Planning assumed the responsibility of publishing the University Fact Book, under Dunn's direction. The office changed its name to the Office of Institutional Research in 1989 and began conducting admissions studies. It changed its name again to the Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation in 2006.
The Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation is responsible for providing research data and information to a variety of decision makers and departments within Tufts University. Along with preparing a range of research survey projects, outcome assessments, and program evaluations, the Office also publishes the University Fact Book and the University Dashboard. Staff members also conduct consultative work in the areas of designing surveys, crafting research proposals, and preparing evaluations.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some retricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection amay require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Administration and Governance -- Planning, evaluation, policies & procedures; Research and Research Administration; Admissions and Recruitment; Alumni and Alumni Relations; Finance
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains surveys, reports, and associated administrative files generated and compiled by the Office of Institutional Research.
  Arrangement
  While material is primarily arranged chronologically, date ranges overlap across different accessions. Until April 2006, material was only arranged by original date ranges. Starting April 2006, files were arranged alphabetically within a date range of accessioned material. As of April 2006, administrative files associated with surveys and reports are moreover filed at the beginning of the alphabetical run. There is no box number 18.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation.
  - Capital Financing Plans, 1985; UA042.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - CIHE Data Forms Update, 1991; UA042.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - 12 Month Comparison, 1982; UA042.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Endowment Projections, 1982; UA042.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Endowment, 1985; UA042.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1979 -- 1980; UA042.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1978 -- 1979; UA042.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1977 -- 1978; UA042.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1976 -- 1977; UA042.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1975 -- 1976; UA042.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1974 -- 1975; UA042.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - [Operations Actual], 1973 -- 1974; UA042.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1972 -- 1973; UA042.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Operations Actual, 1971; UA042.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Preliminary, 1968 -- 1969; UA042.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Income and Expense, 1965 -- 1969; UA042.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Financial Statements Fiscal Yr. Ending, 1972; UA042.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - MHEFA, 1974 -- 1985; UA042.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Treasurer Report, 1972 -- 1981; UA042.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tuition: Setting Criteria, 1984; UA042.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1988; UA042.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1987; UA042.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1986; UA042.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1985; UA042.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1984; UA042.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1983; UA042.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1989; UA042.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1982; UA042.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1981; UA042.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1980; UA042.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1979; UA042.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1978; UA042.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1976; UA042.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1975; UA042.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1974; UA042.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1973; UA042.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1972; UA042.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1971; UA042.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1970; UA042.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1966 -- 1967; UA042.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1965 -- 1966; UA042.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1963 -- 1964; UA042.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1962 -- 1963; UA042.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Financial Statements, 1961 -- 1962; UA042.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Enrollments by Sex and Minority Status, 1974 -- 1984; UA042.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Enrollments Overseas, 1961 -- 1966; UA042.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment: Matrix of Courses Taken w/Passing Grade by Graduating Class and School, 1970 -- 1974; UA042.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment: Courses, 1970 -- 1976; UA042.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment, 1977 -- 1982; UA042.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Enrollment Model, 1983; UA042.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Distributions, 1972; UA042.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Across the University, 1986; UA042.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Across the University, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Across the University, 1986 -- 1987; UA042.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Review, 1986; UA042.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Across the University, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Financial Aid Package Class of, 1991; UA042.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid, 1986; UA042.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Across the University, 1984 -- 1985; UA042.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid - Mass. Family Education Loan Program, 1984; UA042.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Data, 1982 -- 1984; UA042.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
  - Financial Loan Aid Policy - Misc. Correspondence, 1972; UA042.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid - Tuition Remission Comparative Info, 1970 -- 1976; UA042.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid - Scholarship Status and Course Enrollment, 1976; UA042.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid - Policy at MIT, 1973; UA042.001.001.00066 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid - Medical School, 1983; UA042.001.001.00067 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid at Harvard, 1983; UA042.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Study, 1981; UA042.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - Wesleyan Financial Aid and Tuition Studies, 1984; UA042.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Comparion - Tufts/National, 1984; UA042.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Presentation to Academic Affairs, 1986; UA042.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Financial Aid Study, 1985; UA042.001.001.00073 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Financial Aid, 1982; UA042.001.001.00074 (Box 1)
  - Financial Aid Information, 1984 -- 1986; UA042.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Financial Aid Information, 1984 -- 1986; UA042.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - New England Small College Athletic Association, 1971 -- 1974; UA042.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Profile - Liberal Arts and Jackson Graduation Seniors, 1975 -- 1977; UA042.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduation - Plans: Liberal Arts, Jackson, and Engineering, 1971; UA042.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduation - Professional Registration of Engineers, 1968 -- 1974; UA042.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1986; UA042.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate: Admissions to Professional Schools, 1980; UA042.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate: Law Admissions, 1980; UA042.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Grades - BSOT, 1972; UA042.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Grade Distribution, 1976; UA042.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Grading Patterns in Arts and Sciences, 1976 -- 1980; UA042.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Grade Reports, 1977 -- 1978; UA042.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Comparative Resident Costs and Tuition Rates, 1981 -- 1983; UA042.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - [Tuition Rates and Resident Costs], 1978; UA042.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1973 -- 1989; UA042.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1984 -- 1985; UA042.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Tuition Setting Critera, 1984; UA042.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Tuition and Family Income, 1972; UA042.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Academic Difficulty Study, 1986; UA042.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Arts and Sciences Enrollment Proposal, 1981; UA042.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1985; UA042.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Five Year Summary of the Post-Graduate Plans for the Classes of, 1988 -- 1992; UA042.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1986; UA042.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1987; UA042.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1988; UA042.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1989; UA042.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1990; UA042.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1991; UA042.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Post-Graduate Plans, Class of, 1992; UA042.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Institutional Profile, 1983 -- 1988; UA042.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Institutional Profile, 1983 -- 1988; UA042.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Intellectual Property Policies, 1986; UA042.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Sponsored Expenditures, 1984; UA042.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Sponsored Activities, 1987; UA042.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Sponsored Activities, 1987; UA042.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Corporate and Foundation Fund-Raising, 1986 -- 1987; UA042.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Research, 1981 -- 1983; UA042.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Grafton Campus Master Plan, 1986; UA042.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Grafton Campus Planning, 1986; UA042.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Facilities - HSE: Grafton Master Plan, 1980; UA042.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Historical Overview of Grants and Contracts, 1979; UA042.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Vet School - Facilities Housing Questionnaire, 1985; UA042.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Vet School - Pew, 1988; UA042.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Vet School - Pew, 1988; UA042.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Vet School - Comparative Data, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Vet Comparisons, 1984; UA042.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - Vet School, Comparative Data, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - Vet School Comparison, 1986; UA042.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - Vet School, Comparison Data, 1986; UA042.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Vet School, Comparison, 1986 -- 1987; UA042.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Vet School, Comparison Data, 1988; UA042.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Vet School, Admissions Data, 1983; UA042.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Programs: Veterinary Miscellaneous Materials, 1979 -- 1989; UA042.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Notes on the Development of Tufts, Richard M. Freeland, 1900 -- 1940; UA042.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Arts and Science Faculty, Survival Pattern, 1970 -- 1981; UA042.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Enrollments, International Statistics, 1972 -- 1983; UA042.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Traffic and Parking, 1985; UA042.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Tenure Study Committee, 1981; UA042.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Tenure Study Committee, 1981; UA042.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Faculty and Staff: Policies, Conflict of Interest Policy, 1983; UA042.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1989; UA042.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1989; UA042.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Real Estate, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Master Plan, 1986; UA042.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Master Plan, 1986; UA042.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Master Plan, 1986; UA042.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Comparative Vehicle Study, 1988; UA042.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Science and Engineering Facilities, 1987; UA042.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Facilities Comparison, 1986; UA042.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - University Facilities, Boston Campus Housing, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - University Facilities, Boston Campus Housing, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Long-Term Expansion of Research Space, Feasibility and Financial Impact, 1982; UA042.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Facilities Master Plan, 1982 -- 1992; UA042.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Facilities Master Plan, 1982 -- 1992; UA042.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Guidelines for Research, Facility - HNRL - CEM, 1985; UA042.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - University Organization: Personnel, 1983; UA042.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1988; UA042.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Faculty & Staff: Compensation: AAUP Report, 1970 -- 1971; UA042.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Compensation Comparison of Tufts Schools, 1971 -- 1972; UA042.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Faculty & Staff: Compensation Miscellanous Data, 1972 -- 1982; UA042.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1984 -- 1985; UA042.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Section: Vet Salary Study, 1983; UA042.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Faculty & Staff Outside Activities, Faculty Outside Activities & Earnings, 1981 -- 1984; UA042.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Faculty & Staff: Policy, Outside Activites, 1984; UA042.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Conflict of Interest Policies, 1988; UA042.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty & Staff: Policies Guidelines on Commercial Involvement, 1981; UA042.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, 1990; UA042.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Comment Letters, 1990; UA042.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Comments, 1990; UA042.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Senior Comments, 1990; UA042.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Comparative Data, 1990; UA042.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, 1990; UA042.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Majors by Race, 1988 -- 1990; UA042.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Preview, 1990; UA042.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Satisfaction, 1990; UA042.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, Advising Data, 1990; UA042.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, Post-Graduate Plans, 1990; UA042.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Majors by SAT, 1990; UA042.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Individuals Willing to Participate in Alumni Network, 1990; UA042.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, Advising Report, 1990; UA042.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey - 2nd Half (employment/grad. school list), 1990; UA042.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey: Financial Report, 1990; UA042.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey - Satisfaction with Tufts Facilities by Resident in Experiment Status, 1990; UA042.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey: Importance of Career Decisions, 1990; UA042.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey: Evaluation and Satisfaction with Undergraduate Education, 1990; UA042.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Distribution, 1990; UA042.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Breakdowns, 1989; UA042.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Reactions/Suggestions, 1984; UA042.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, 1988; UA042.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Information, 1989; UA042.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, 1988; UA042.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Satisfaction, 1989; UA042.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Board of Overseers for Student Life, 1990; UA042.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey - Draft, 1989; UA042.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey Instrument, 1984; UA042.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, 1989; UA042.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey - Comparisons, 1989; UA042.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey, 1989; UA042.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey - Preview, 1989; UA042.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey - HEDS, 1989; UA042.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Senior Survey - Preview, 1988; UA042.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - 12 College Comparison, 1986; UA042.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
  - Sackler Comparative Study, 1986; UA042.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
  - Comparative Studies: Vet School, 1988; UA042.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Programs, 1984; UA042.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Student Quality, 1984; UA042.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Tuitions and Aid, 1983 -- 1984; UA042.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Private Support, 1977 -- 1983; UA042.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Budget Data, 1982 -- 1984; UA042.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Libraries, 1981 -- 1982; UA042.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Federal Funding, 1975 -- 1982; UA042.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Faculty, 1984; UA042.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Endowments, 1982 -- 1984; UA042.001.004.00056 (Box 4)
  - Twelve College Comparison - Enrollments, 1982 -- 1984; UA042.001.004.00057 (Box 4)
  - Alumni - All Questions by High School Type Class of, 1982; UA042.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Evaluation Experience by Major Class of, 1982; UA042.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Graduate Institutions Class of, 1982; UA042.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Acceptance Stage Competitors Class of, 1982; UA042.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1982, by Gender, UA042.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1982, Documents, UA042.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of 1982, Originals, UA042.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1982, Data Entry, UA042.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1982, Correspondence, 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Current Activities by Major, 1992; UA042.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Current Activities by Major, 1992; UA042.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Data Entry, UA042.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Current Position, Degree, and Institution by Major, UA042.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of, 1986; UA042.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of, 1992; UA042.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of 1986, Correspondence, 1992; UA042.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of 1986, Response to Question 52, 1992; UA042.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Question 51, Alumni's Willingness to Participate, 1992; UA042.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Additional Responses to Questions, 1992; UA042.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Surveys, 1992; UA042.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of 1986, 1991; UA042.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of 1986, Evaluation of Undergraduate Experiences, 1992; UA042.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, Originals, 1992; UA042.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Alumni - Class of 1986, International Relation Majors, 1992; UA042.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Fund Information, 1991; UA042.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Evaluation of Undergraduate Experiences, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Minority Correspondences, 1992; UA042.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Minority Survey Instrument, Originals, 1992; UA042.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of, 1992; UA042.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of, 1992; UA042.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of, 1992; UA042.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey - Class of, 1992; UA042.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Senior Suvey, List of Best Course and Professor Nominations, 1992; UA042.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Nominations, List of nominations used for chairs and individuals, 1993; UA042.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Nominations, List of faculty list for best course, Originals, 1993; UA042.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Nominations, List of best course by department, 1993; UA042.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Senior Survey -- Best, Course Nominations, 1993; UA042.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - AIDS and Drug Abuse Survey, Originals, 1993; UA042.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Senior Survey, Sex, Drugs, and STD's, 1993; UA042.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Engineering Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Alumni Career Advisor Network, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Athletics, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Career Planning Service, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Evaluation of Tufts services, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Data Sharings [HEDS], Comparartive Data, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Data Sharings [HEDS], Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Internships, Political Science, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Pre-Major Advising, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Majors by Race, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Minors, Evaluation of, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Best Course, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Post-Graduate Plans for the Class, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Preview, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Post-Graduate Plans for the Class of 1988-94, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Ethnicity, Responses by, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Trends, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Graphs, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Graphs, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Graphs, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Graphs, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Previews, Senior Survey, 1994; UA042.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Evaluation of Undergraduate Majors, Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Evaluation of Undergraduate Majors, Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Evaluation of Undergraduate Majors, Senior Survey, 1991; UA042.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Programs: Dental Long-Range Planning Report, 1978; UA042.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Programs: Dental Four-Year Curriculum Plan, 1979; UA042.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Programs: Proposed Four-Year Curriculum, 1980; UA042.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Programs: Dental Proposed Three-Year Curriculum, 1980 -- 1983; UA042.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Programs: Dental School Plans, 1983; UA042.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - NERB Results, 1987; UA042.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Market Data, 1987; UA042.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Dental: Patient Pathway, 1986; UA042.001.006.00034 (Box 6)